

Caio Moreira

São Paulo - SP. Brazil

□ +55 (11) 97501-9555 | ☑ caiovitor.moreira@hotmail.com | ☐ caiom2r | ☐ caiovmoreira

About Me.

I've been working with data for over 2 years, focusing on Data Science and Machine Learning applications. I'm currently working on developing Cloud products to help companies innovate through Artificial Intelligence and use data to make better-informed decisions. I love AI and how it can help people in so many different ways, and that's why it has been my favorite study subject lately.

Education

USP - University of São Paulo

São Paulo, Brazil

B.Sc. Information Systems

Mar. 2017 - Dec. 2020

Skills

Programming Python, SQL, C/C++, Java, R

Languages English (Fluent), Portuguese (First Language)

Other Skills Pandas, scikit-learn, Linux, Git, TensorFlow, CUDA, Power BI, Metabase, ETL, GCP, Statistics, MongoDB

Experience

Accenture São Paulo, Brazil

Data & Al

Sep. 2020 - Ongoing

• Developing data products on the cloud, focusing on Google Cloud Platform's solutions. Using Python, SQL and Deep Learning Frameworks (mostly TensorFlow) to solve business problems alogside different teams to help several national and international clients.

Netshoes São Paulo, Brazil

DATA SCIENCE INTERN

Nov. 2018 - Sep. 2019

• The main job tool was Python, it was used for data handling, analysis, studies and Machine Learning algorithm development. Our daily routine was guided by Agile Methodologies fundamentals. I was able to use several Cloud tools to implement ETL routines and data visualization solutions. Also, I used GitHub for code versioning.

Certificates

Coursera

DEEPLEARNING.AI TENSORFLOW DEVELOPER

Nov. 2020

- A series of courses that shows the best way to use TensorFlow to provide meaningful results with real world data. Covers the implementation of Neural Networks (DNNs, CNNs, RNNs and LSTMs) and ways to optimize and evaluate the results to deal with NLP, Computer Vision, Time Series and Categorical and Numeric Data problems.
- · Click here to see the Certificate

Udemy

Machine Learning A-Z
Out. 2019

- Focus on developing Machine Learning models, with explanations on how the algorithms work. Content covered from Regressions up to Neural Networks using Python as the main development tool.
- Click here to see the Certificate